rockyoumedia.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy – RockYou

Privacy Policy  [Pinsuda Singchai](https://rockyou.com/author/pinsuda-singchai/ "Posts by Pinsuda Singchai") 2018-10-24T09:42:35+00:00 

**RockYou Privacy Policy**

RockYou, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively, “RockYou”) provides a host of websites, gaming applications, mobile applications and other gaming services, as well as a technology that allows our partners to show ads to the users of those games. RockYou recognize that its customers, visitors, users, and others (collectively or individually “Users”) who use games, applications, websites, and other services provided by RockYou (collectively, the “RockYou Sites”) as well as visitors to our partners’ games and applications value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of User information collected on the RockYou Sites and other sites and services that integrate RockYou technology.

**THE INFORMATION ROCKYOU COLLECTS**

**Information You Provide Us**

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the RockYou Sites, fill out a form, participate in a contest or promotion, make a purchase, apply for a job, communicate with us via third-party social media sites, request customer support, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number, financial information (credit card number, expiration date and security code), and any other information you choose to provide.

When you use the RockYou Sites on Facebook or use your login credentials from Facebook or another social network service, we may collect and record the information you provide us voluntarily through Facebook or other social network service in accordance with the policies and terms of Facebook or other social network service and your settings with that service. The types of personal information collected may vary depending on your activity, social network settings, and the permissions you grant, but may include your name, Facebook user identification number, email address, gender, current city, profile picture, and age or date of birth.

In the event that you wish to claim a prize won through one of RockYou’s rewards-based gaming applications (e.g., Bingo by Ryzing), you will need to follow certain procedures set forth in the terms of such application. Some of these procedures may include the submission of certain personal information, such as your photo identification or Social Security Number.

**Location Data**

If you consent to allow a RockYou Site or one of our partners access information about your location, we may collect information about your precise location and share it with third parties for the purpose showing ads that are targeted to your interests. We also use your IP address to derive information about your general location (for example, your city or town).

**Automatically Collected Information**

When you interact with a RockYou Site or a website, mobile application, or other gaming service that integrates RockYou’s technology, we collect certain information about your mobile device or computer system, including your browser type, browser language, platform type, MAC Address, IP Address, mobile advertising ID, Facebook ID, cookie information, and information about your interactions with the RockYou Sites or other apps or games that integrate RockYou’s technology, such as referring / exit pages and URLs, clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order in which those pages were viewed, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of your request.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We and our partners, affiliates, and analytics and other providers use technologies such as cookies, beacons, pixels, tags, scripts, and SDKs to analyze trends, administer the RockYou Sites, advertise, and to gather demographic information about our users. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

Cookies are a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters that help us improve the RockYou Sites and your experience, see which areas and features of the RockYou Sites are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in the RockYou Sites or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. An SDK is a piece of computer code that developers include in their mobile applications.

**Information We Collect from Other Sources**

RockYou and partners that use RockYou technology may obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through the RockYou Sites or our partners’ services. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including but not limited to game partners, identity verification services, advertisers, mailing list providers, and publicly available sources.

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS**

RockYou allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the RockYou Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, device, or mobile application, the advertisements and links that appear on the RockYou Sites or our partners’ sites. These third parties automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, SDKs, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. RockYou does not provide any personal information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks RockYou to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the target audience.

**USE OF INFORMATION**

We use the information we collect to operate, maintain, and provide you the features and functionality of the RockYou Sites. We also use the information we collect to show ads and report on how they perform, including to show ads that are targeted to users’ interests across their devices, limiting the number of times users see ads, customizing ads to users’ locations, determining how users respond to ads, and reporting on the effectiveness of ads. Finally, we use the data we collect to protect the rights of RockYou and others, including to detect, prevent, investigate, and deter fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

RockYou will not share, sell, rent or trade information that identifies you other than as described in this privacy policy. RockYou may share information that identifies you as follows:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;
  * When you post information publicly, such as in discussion boards, messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc., that information will be publicly available;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law or legal process, including lawful requests by public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of RockYou or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company;
  * Between and among RockYou and our current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and other companies under common control and ownership; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

In addition, companies that use RockYou’s technology to collect data about their users will have access to that data and may use it for their own purposes, and may share such data with third parties such as advertising partners. Finally, we may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

**YOUR CHOICES**

**Public Profiles**

The profiles you create and any content that you post on the RockYou Sites will be publicly accessible unless otherwise indicated. You may change the privacy settings of your profile through your account portal. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@rockyou.com](mailto:privacy@rockyou.com).

**Location Information**

When you first launch any of our applications that collect location information, you will be asked to consent to the application’s collection of this information. If you initially consent to our collection of location information, you can subsequently stop the collection of this information at any time by changing the preferences on your mobile device.

**Cookie Information**

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the RockYou Sites.

**Targeted Advertising**

To opt out of the use of information about your web browsing activity to show ads that are targeted to your interests by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, or if you are in the EU <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>. To opt out of use of information about your app usage for purposes of showing ads that are targeted to your interests, please use the settings on your device (“Limit Ad Tracking” on iOS or “Opt Out of Interest-Based Ads” or “Opt Out of Ads Personalization” on Android).

**Promotional Communications**

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the instructions in those messages or by emailing us at [privacy@rockyou.com](mailto:privacy@rockyou.com). If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

**Mobile/Push Notifications**

We may also occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications to send you game updates, high scores and other service related notifications that may be of importance to you. You may at any time opt out from receiving these types of communications by turning them off on the app or at the device level through your settings.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

The RockYou Sites include links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of RockYou. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to RockYou. For that reason, RockYou does not knowingly collect or maintain information on the RockYou Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no RockYou Sites are directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use or access the RockYou Sites at any time or in any manner. If RockYou learns that personal information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the RockYou Sites then RockYou will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

**INTERNATIONAL USERS & PRIVACY SHIELD**

The RockYou Sites are hosted in the United States. If you access the RockYou Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from the laws of the United States, please be advised that through your continued use of the RockYou Sites, you are transferring your personal information to the United States.

RockYou (and its subsidiaries) participate in and have certified compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. RockYou is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List. <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>

RockYou is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives under the Privacy Shield Framework and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. RockYou complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, RockYou is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, RockYou may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**DATA RETENTION**

We store the information we collect about you for as long as is necessary for the purposes for which we originally collected it, such as to mediate your access to the RockYou Sites, for advertising, or as needed to provide you services. We also retain your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

We do not share personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure. California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at [privacy@rockyou.com](mailto:privacy@rockyou.com).

**RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), you have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal data.

**Legal Basis for Processing**

If you are a resident of the EEA, when we process your personal data we will only do so in the following situations:

  * When we have your consent to do so, such as if you consent to allow us to show ads that are targeted to your interests based on your visits to websites, apps, or games with which we work to show ads.
  * We need to use your personal data to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., processing payments for and providing the RockYou services you have requested).
  * We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data. For example, we may process your personal data to send you marketing communications, to communicate with you about changes to the RockYou Sites, and to provide, secure, and improve the RockYou Sites.

**Data Subject Requests**

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the right to access personal data we hold about you and to ask that your personal data be corrected, erased, or transferred. You may also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, you may contact us as indicated below.

**Questions or Complaints**

If you are a resident of the EEA and have a concern about our processing of personal data that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data privacy authority where you reside. For contact details of your local Data Protection Authority, please see: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm>.

**CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically reflected by the “effective date” below. Please revisit this page frequently to become aware of any changes. If we materially change how we use your personal information, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

**Date Last Modified:**

This Privacy Policy was last modified October 23, 2018

**Contact Information:**

Please contact RockYou with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the RockYou Sites by emailing: [privacy@rockyou.com](mailto:privacy@rockyou.com).

RockYou, Inc.  
1111 Broadway, FL 3  
Oakland, CA 94607

**RockYou Privacy Policy**

RockYou, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively, “RockYou”) provides a host of websites, gaming applications, mobile applications and other gaming services, as well as a technology that allows our partners to show ads to the users of those games. RockYou recognize that its customers, visitors, users, and others (collectively or individually “Users”) who use games, applications, websites, and other services provided by RockYou (collectively, the “RockYou Sites”) as well as visitors to our partners’ games and applications value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of User information collected on the RockYou Sites and other sites and services that integrate RockYou technology.

**THE INFORMATION ROCKYOU COLLECTS**

**Information You Provide Us**

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the RockYou Sites, fill out a form, participate in a contest or promotion, make a purchase, apply for a job, communicate with us via third-party social media sites, request customer support, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number, financial information (credit card number, expiration date and security code), and any other information you choose to provide.

When you use the RockYou Sites on Facebook or use your login credentials from Facebook or another social network service, we may collect and record the information you provide us voluntarily through Facebook or other social network service in accordance with the policies and terms of Facebook or other social network service and your settings with that service. The types of personal information collected may vary depending on your activity, social network settings, and the permissions you grant, but may include your name, Facebook user identification number, email address, gender, current city, profile picture, and age or date of birth.

In the event that you wish to claim a prize won through one of RockYou’s rewards-based gaming applications (e.g., Bingo by Ryzing), you will need to follow certain procedures set forth in the terms of such application. Some of these procedures may include the submission of certain personal information, such as your photo identification or Social Security Number.

**Location Data**

If you consent to allow a RockYou Site or one of our partners access information about your location, we may collect information about your precise location and share it with third parties for the purpose showing ads that are targeted to your interests. We also use your IP address to derive information about your general location (for example, your city or town).

**Automatically Collected Information**

When you interact with a RockYou Site or a website, mobile application, or other gaming service that integrates RockYou’s technology, we collect certain information about your mobile device or computer system, including your browser type, browser language, platform type, MAC Address, IP Address, mobile advertising ID, Facebook ID, cookie information, and information about your interactions with the RockYou Sites or other apps or games that integrate RockYou’s technology, such as referring / exit pages and URLs, clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order in which those pages were viewed, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of your request.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We and our partners, affiliates, and analytics and other providers use technologies such as cookies, beacons, pixels, tags, scripts, and SDKs to analyze trends, administer the RockYou Sites, advertise, and to gather demographic information about our users. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

Cookies are a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters that help us improve the RockYou Sites and your experience, see which areas and features of the RockYou Sites are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in the RockYou Sites or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. An SDK is a piece of computer code that developers include in their mobile applications.

**Information We Collect from Other Sources**

RockYou and partners that use RockYou technology may obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through the RockYou Sites or our partners’ services. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including but not limited to game partners, identity verification services, advertisers, mailing list providers, and publicly available sources.

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS**

RockYou allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the RockYou Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, device, or mobile application, the advertisements and links that appear on the RockYou Sites or our partners’ sites. These third parties automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, SDKs, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. RockYou does not provide any personal information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks RockYou to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the target audience.

**USE OF INFORMATION**

We use the information we collect to operate, maintain, and provide you the features and functionality of the RockYou Sites. We also use the information we collect to show ads and report on how they perform, including to show ads that are targeted to users’ interests across their devices, limiting the number of times users see ads, customizing ads to users’ locations, determining how users respond to ads, and reporting on the effectiveness of ads. Finally, we use the data we collect to protect the rights of RockYou and others, including to detect, prevent, investigate, and deter fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

RockYou will not share, sell, rent or trade information that identifies you other than as described in this privacy policy. RockYou may share information that identifies you as follows:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;
  * When you post information publicly, such as in discussion boards, messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc., that information will be publicly available;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law or legal process, including lawful requests by public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of RockYou or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company;
  * Between and among RockYou and our current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and other companies under common control and ownership; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

In addition, companies that use RockYou’s technology to collect data about their users will have access to that data and may use it for their own purposes, and may share such data with third parties such as advertising partners. Finally, we may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

**YOUR CHOICES**

**Public Profiles**

The profiles you create and any content that you post on the RockYou Sites will be publicly accessible unless otherwise indicated. You may change the privacy settings of your profile through your account portal. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@rockyou.com](mailto:privacy@rockyou.com).

**Location Information**

When you first launch any of our applications that collect location information, you will be asked to consent to the application’s collection of this information. If you initially consent to our collection of location information, you can subsequently stop the collection of this information at any time by changing the preferences on your mobile device.

**Cookie Information**

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the RockYou Sites.

**Targeted Advertising**

To opt out of the use of information about your web browsing activity to show ads that are targeted to your interests by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, or if you are in the EU <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>. To opt out of use of information about your app usage for purposes of showing ads that are targeted to your interests, please use the settings on your device (“Limit Ad Tracking” on iOS or “Opt Out of Interest-Based Ads” or “Opt Out of Ads Personalization” on Android).

**Promotional Communications**

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the instructions in those messages or by emailing us at [privacy@rockyou.com](mailto:privacy@rockyou.com). If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

**Mobile/Push Notifications**

We may also occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications to send you game updates, high scores and other service related notifications that may be of importance to you. You may at any time opt out from receiving these types of communications by turning them off on the app or at the device level through your settings.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

The RockYou Sites include links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of RockYou. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to RockYou. For that reason, RockYou does not knowingly collect or maintain information on the RockYou Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no RockYou Sites are directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use or access the RockYou Sites at any time or in any manner. If RockYou learns that personal information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the RockYou Sites then RockYou will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

**INTERNATIONAL USERS & PRIVACY SHIELD**

The RockYou Sites are hosted in the United States. If you access the RockYou Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from the laws of the United States, please be advised that through your continued use of the RockYou Sites, you are transferring your personal information to the United States.

RockYou (and its subsidiaries) participate in and have certified compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. RockYou is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List. <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>

RockYou is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives under the Privacy Shield Framework and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. RockYou complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, RockYou is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, RockYou may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**DATA RETENTION**

We store the information we collect about you for as long as is necessary for the purposes for which we originally collected it, such as to mediate your access to the RockYou Sites, for advertising, or as needed to provide you services. We also retain your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

We do not share personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure. California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at [privacy@rockyou.com](mailto:privacy@rockyou.com).

**RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), you have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal data.

**Legal Basis for Processing**

If you are a resident of the EEA, when we process your personal data we will only do so in the following situations:

  * When we have your consent to do so, such as if you consent to allow us to show ads that are targeted to your interests based on your visits to websites, apps, or games with which we work to show ads.
  * We need to use your personal data to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., processing payments for and providing the RockYou services you have requested).
  * We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data. For example, we may process your personal data to send you marketing communications, to communicate with you about changes to the RockYou Sites, and to provide, secure, and improve the RockYou Sites.

**Data Subject Requests**

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the right to access personal data we hold about you and to ask that your personal data be corrected, erased, or transferred. You may also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, you may contact us as indicated below.

**Questions or Complaints**

If you are a resident of the EEA and have a concern about our processing of personal data that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data privacy authority where you reside. For contact details of your local Data Protection Authority, please see: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm>.

**CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically reflected by the “effective date” below. Please revisit this page frequently to become aware of any changes. If we materially change how we use your personal information, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

**Date Last Modified:**

This Privacy Policy was last modified October 23, 2018

**Contact Information:**

Please contact RockYou with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the RockYou Sites by emailing: [privacy@rockyou.com](mailto:privacy@rockyou.com).

RockYou, Inc.  
1111 Broadway, FL 3  
Oakland, CA 94607
